[{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f0311339bd1","question_no_e":"2686","question":"Which ABBA song won the 1974 Eurovision Song Contest?","answer":"Waterloo","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.545Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5cde129f031133b975","question_no_m":"1186","question":"Which Birthsign spans the months of January and February?","answer":"Aquarius","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:56.847Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a674","question_no_g":"810","question":"Which state is located between Maine and Vermont?","answer":"New Hampshire","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.388Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a597","question_no_g":"589","question":"What do folks from Louisiana and Mississippi call sluggish creeks and marshy lakes?","answer":"Bayous","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.316Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5dde129f031133c70d","question_no_s":"1232","question":"What \"-itis\" is an inflammation of the liver?","answer":"Hepatitis","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:57.890Z"},{"_id":"5867fd59de129f0311338efc","question_no_a":"1677","question":"Which literary work's title character is named Frankie Addams?","answer":"The Member of the Wedding","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["arts"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:53.494Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a7d9","question_no_g":"1167","question":"What island nation was ruled by \"Papa Doc\" and \"Baby Doc\" Duvalier?","answer":"Haiti","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.501Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5dde129f031133c37c","question_no_s":"319","question":"Who developed the classification we use for clouds?","answer":"Luke Howard","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:57.616Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ede129f031133c9f2","question_no_s":"1974","question":"Metamorphic, sedimentary, and igneous are types of what?","answer":"Rocks","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:58.119Z"},{"_id":"5867fd59de129f0311338d89","question_no_a":"1306","question":"What original literary work was the movie \"Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory\" based on?","answer":"Charlie and the Chocolate Factory","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["arts"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:53.373Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5dde129f031133bbb7","question_no_m":"1764","question":"What is the largest football stadium in Brazil?","answer":"The Maracana stadium","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:57.022Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a96b","question_no_g":"1569","question":"What is the only Asian country whose common name is only one syllable?","answer":"Laos","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.618Z"},{"_id":"5867fd58de129f031133888f","question_no_a":"30","question":"Who is Othello's wife?","answer":"Desdemona","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["arts"],"tags":["Plays","Tragedies","Shakespeare","Literary Characters"],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:52.857Z"},{"_id":"5867fd58de129f0311338904","question_no_a":"149","question":"What form of theater was the subject of many of Degas' paintings?","answer":"Ballet","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["arts"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:52.924Z"},{"_id":"5867fd59de129f0311339199","question_no_e":"70","question":"What instrument does Meg White play in the band White Stripes?","answer":"Drums","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:53.702Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a3ba","question_no_g":"112","question":"Which is the world's northernmost capital city?","answer":"Reykjavik","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.170Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f0311339d1f","question_no_e":"3020","question":"What sport is the focus of the movie \"The Color of Money\"?","answer":"Pool","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.645Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f0311339b4c","question_no_e":"2553","question":"What mode of transportation did Gary Numan sing about in a 1980 Top 10 hit?","answer":"Cars","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.509Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5cde129f031133aeef","question_no_h":"710","question":"Who commanded the English Fleet against the Spanish Armada in 1588?","answer":"Admiral Charles Howard","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["history"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:56.045Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f031133957c","question_no_e":"1065","question":"What won an Emmy for outstanding music direction in 1985?","answer":"Christmas In Washington","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.052Z"},{"_id":"5867fd59de129f0311338f1f","question_no_a":"1712","question":"What author created Discworld?","answer":"Terry Pratchett","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["arts"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:53.506Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f0311339f1d","question_no_e":"3530","question":"Who has been played in a movie by both John Cusack and Edward Norton?","answer":"Nelson Rockefeller","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.796Z"},{"_id":"590679e4ff9c0647b50a8052","question_no_a":"1","question":"What network was primarily responsible for leaking over 11.5 million documents, collectively known as the Panama Papers, on April 3, 2016?","answer":"The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["history"],"tags":["2016","2010s","2000s"],"created":1493596644767},{"_id":"5867fd59de129f0311338c80","question_no_a":"1041","question":"\"The Cardinal of the Kremlin\" is the sequel to what 1984 Tom Clancy novel?","answer":"The Hunt for Red October","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["arts"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:53.273Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5dde129f031133bb85","question_no_m":"1714","question":"What businessman served as manager of the Atlanta Braves for one game in 1977?","answer":"Ted Turner","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:57.007Z"},{"_id":"5904998ccf93664eb1048692","question_no_a":"1","question":"Which famous actor is honored with a statue in Leicester Square?","answer":"Charlie Chaplin","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["arts"],"tags":["Actors","Statues"],"created":1493473676781},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f0311339f33","question_no_e":"3552","question":"Which band member of Red Hot Chili Peppers died of drug overdose?","answer":"Hillel Slovak","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.802Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ede129f031133c8b5","question_no_s":"1656","question":"Proteus orbits what planet of the solar system?","answer":"Neptune","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:58.023Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ede129f031133c8fa","question_no_s":"1726","question":"What is an erythrocyte?","answer":"Red blood cell","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:58.045Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5dde129f031133c84c","question_no_s":"1551","question":"In what organ of the human body would you find the Eustachian tube?","answer":"The ear","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:57.992Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f031133a02a","question_no_e":"3799","question":"In the TV show \"Family Guy\", Franz Gutentag was once what?","answer":"A Nazi war criminal","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.882Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ede129f031133ca61","question_no_s":"2085","question":"What name is given to the diagram in which sets are represented by circles?","answer":"Venn DiagramÂ ","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:58.149Z"},{"_id":"5867fd59de129f0311338a5a","question_no_a":"491","question":"What is the name of the character that can be used in place of the word \"and\"?","answer":"Ampersand","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["arts"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:53.063Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5dde129f031133c666","question_no_s":"1065","question":"The sub-atomic particle \"proton\" has what type of charge?","answer":"Positive","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:57.840Z"},{"_id":"58ec23668dc25ca9e12ef630","question_no_a":"1","question":"In what sport is the ball 40 millimetres in diameter and weighs 2.7 grams?","answer":"Table Tennis","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":["Sports","Table Tennis"],"created":1491870566912},{"_id":"5867fd5cde129f031133b4ef","question_no_m":"28","question":"What does P.S. stand for at the end of a letter?","answer":"Postscript","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:56.508Z"},{"_id":"5867fd59de129f0311339311","question_no_e":"446","question":"In the movie \"Dirty Dancing\", what did Baby carry?","answer":"A watermelon","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:53.825Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f03113395ce","question_no_e":"1147","question":"Which \"Simpsons\" character is missing an arm?","answer":"Herman","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.077Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5cde129f031133bb51","question_no_m":"1662","question":"Founded in 1911, what company was first known as the Computing Tabulating  Recording Corporation?","answer":"IBM","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:56.991Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5dde129f031133c462","question_no_s":"549","question":"The Hawaiian landmark known as \"Diamond Head\" was formed from what?","answer":"Magma","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["science"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:57.683Z"},{"_id":"590721e13745b36be73039fb","question_no_a":"1","question":"Which Disney character is named after Ebenezer from Charles Dickensâ novel \"A Christmas Carol\"?","answer":"Scrooge McDuck","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":["Holidays","Christmas","Disney","Literary characters"],"created":1493639649516},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f03113398f6","question_no_e":"1955","question":"What Beatles song begins with the opening fanfare from the French national anthem?","answer":"All You Need is Love","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.315Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133adcc","question_no_h":"419","question":"Which British liner did a German U-boat sink on May 7th 1915?","answer":"RMS Lusitania","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["history"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.955Z"},{"_id":"5e94d21b5ea27d7a1303aed8","question_no_a":"1","question":"What two players were selected before Michael Jordan in the 1984 NBA Draft?","answer":"Akeem Olajuwon and Sam Bowie","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":["Sports","Basketball"],"created":1586811419791},{"_id":"5867fd5cde129f031133b159","question_no_h":"1328","question":"How did Princess Diana die in 1997?","answer":"Car accident","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["history"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:56.229Z"},{"_id":"59774433284458f1d785442e","question_no_a":"1","question":"The original name of New York City was what?","answer":"New Amsterdam","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["history"],"tags":["United States","New York"],"created":1500988467443},{"_id":"58b371481c3f17ccc40c8e1e","question_no_a":"1","question":"Approximately how much more beer would you get in a pint served in the UK compared to one served in the US?","answer":"95 mL","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":["Bars","Alcohol","Beer","Measurements","Units"],"created":1488154952009},{"_id":"5867fd5dde129f031133beaa","question_no_m":"2519","question":"What cousin of the glockenspiel was named for its ethereal, \"heavenly\" sound?","answer":"The celesta","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:57.248Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f0311339cb0","question_no_e":"2909","question":"What breed of dog is Santa's Little Helper?","answer":"Greyhound","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.611Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5ade129f0311339eaf","question_no_e":"3420","question":"What screen legend made his final appearance in the movie \"Witness for the Prosecution\"?","answer":"Tyrone Power","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:54.764Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5cde129f031133bac7","question_no_m":"1524","question":"Which superheroâs powers could be taken away by the color yellow?","answer":"Green Lantern","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["general"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:56.954Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5cde129f031133afc9","question_no_h":"928","question":"By what name is the Vieux Carre in New Orleans better known?","answer":"French Quarter","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["history"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:56.111Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a910","question_no_g":"1478","question":"What major river runs through Melbourne?","answer":"Yarra","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.591Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133abee","question_no_g":"2212","question":"What is the capital of Ukraine?","answer":"Kiev","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.809Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a57d","question_no_g":"563","question":"Kodiak Island is the largest island in which US state?","answer":"Alaska","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.309Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5cde129f031133b1e4","question_no_h":"1467","question":"Which US president lived in Springwood?","answer":"Franklin Roosevelt","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["history"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:56.269Z"},{"_id":"5e72cf56d0874f1a5e2d1c2a","question_no_a":"1","question":"As of 2020, what actor has portrayed Peter Parker/Spider-Man in the most number of live-action films?","answer":"Tom Holland","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":["Movies","Comic books","Actors"],"created":1584582486244},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a586","question_no_g":"572","question":"What is the capital of the US state of Iowa?","answer":"Des Moines","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.311Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a3a2","question_no_g":"88","question":"What is the official language of Egypt?","answer":"Arabic","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["geography"],"tags":["Languages","Egypt","Africa"],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.163Z"},{"_id":"5867fd5bde129f031133a241","question_no_e":"4334","question":"Who played Inspector Morse in the TV series by the same name?","answer":"John Thaw","user":"560090f391faf44c0952430a","categories":["entertainment"],"tags":[],"created":"2016-12-31T18:47:55.056Z"}]